Mohit Maddhesiya | CV

New Ashok Nagar, New Delhi, 110096

Summary

TOTAL 1.4+ YEARS OF STARTUP EXPERIENCE IN DIVERSE DOMAINS AND TECHNOLOGIES.

I possess very good programming skills as well as the ability to develop multiple logics for solutions. Using any particular programming language has never been a bar for me yet my area of expertise are Java programming languages and JavaScript

Have been an average+ student throughout my academics and taking part in co-curricular activities since schools. Some of my favorite leisure activities are problem solving and playing badminton activities.

Experience

Software Developer @ Crisp Analytics Pvt. Ltd, Noida

June 2015- Oct 2016

- Working as a Data processing layer , delving into intelligent data analysis, data processing, and visualisation, on a daily basis.
- Principles of predictive analytics, and statistica lanalysis were heavily applied and deployed.
- Timely, and regular, delivery of the product (tikali Energy Usage Profiling Project) based on a scrum methodology.
- Module wise development using nodejs and angularjs.

Intern @ Crisp Analytics Pvt. Ltd, Noida

January 2015 - Jun 2015

- Module wise development using codeigniter.

Technical Competencies

- o Programming Languages: Proficient in: Java, Php, JavaScript, HTML.
- Industry Software / Framework: AngularJS, NodeJs, Ionic, Spring, Kafka, Storm, Maven, Codeigniter, Bootstrap, Git
- o Databases: Mysql , Postgres
- o **Environment:** Linux, Eclipse, Tomcat
- Other: Data Structures

Notable Work

Tikali Energy Usage Profiling Project:

Java, Maven, Spring, Kafka, Tomcat, Storm, Postgres, Orientdb, R shiny, ggplot2 d3.js, OpenCPU

A project to detect anomalies in power consumption at 1000s of locations in France and US. Energy Consumption Profiling based on predictive and statistical analysis.

Stanmax Project:

Nodejs, Angularjs, Scala, Hadoop, Azkaban, Excel-macro, Postgres, Monogdb.

Merchandise planning based on historical analysis .Retail Merchandiser Planning System that is plan for goods and area for future base on last year and last to last year. Merchandiser analyses data to set selling price and plan promotions and price reduces. Reporting tool for a retail store for their transactions

O Grap education Project:

Codeigniter, AnualarJS, MySql

Grap education is an e-commerce website. It provides online courses.

o FastPay Project:

Ionic, Php, Mysql

The project focuses at providing an easy and reliable platform to recharge mobile of any telecommunication company through android app without buying recharge card.

o IMS CHAI Project:

Codeigniter, MySql.

IMS CHAI web application that is designed to track the inventory of Pharmaceutical suppliers to DAC from suppliers through to end users (patients) including dispensation to patients.

Education

Master of Computer Application

2012-2015

National Institute of Technology (NIT), Kurukshetra

Bachelor of Computer Application

2011-2014

Maharshi Dayanand University, Rohtak

Interests and extra-curricular activity

- o Programming Languages: have been a constant stalker of hackerearth and geeksforgeeks
- Playing Badminton: have got district level winner.

References

Vaibhav Dobriyal

Vice President Research and Development | Crisp Analytics Mobile: +91.8527116444 | Email: vaibhav@crispanalytics.com